

const Questions = [
    {
        "id" : 1,
        "question" : "Who build Linus?",
        "answer" : "Linus Torvalds",
        "op1" : "Bill Gates",
        "op2" : "Linus Torvalds",
        "op3" : "Vitalik Buterin",
        "op4" : "Mark Zuckerberg",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 2,
        "question" : "Which combination can be used for making a p-type junction?",
        "answer" : "Silicon and Aluminium",
        "op1" : "Sodium and Chorine",
        "op2" : "Silicon and Phosphorus",
        "op3" : "Silicon and Aluminium",
        "op4" : "Germanium and Iron",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 3,
        "question" : "1/1^2 + 1/2^2 + 1/3^2 + 1/4^2 +1/5^2 + 1/6^2 +  .... =?",
        "answer" : "π^2/6",
        "op1" : "e/2",
        "op2" : "π^2/6",
        "op3" : "e^2/2",
        "op4" : "-1/6",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 4,
        "question" : "1+1=?",
        "answer" : "11",
        "op1" : "11",
        "op2" : "3",
        "op3" : "2",
        "op4" : "2^31 - 1",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 5,
        "question" : "Who wrote HitchHiker's Guide to the Galaxy?",
        "answer" : "Adam Douglas",
        "op1" : "Dan Brown",
        "op2" : "Adam Douglas",
        "op3" : "Ruskin Bond",
        "op4" : "Peter Theil",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 6,
        "question" : "Which of the following is a frontend framework?",
        "answer" : "Angular",
        "op1" : "Django",
        "op2" : "Angular",
        "op3" : "Express",
        "op4" : "Flask",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 7,
        "question" : "Which of the following is the best possible way of extracting energy from an object ",
        "answer" : "Colliding the body near black hole",
        "op1" : "Nuclear Reactions",
        "op2" : "Colliding the body near black hole",
        "op3" : "Starting at the object",
        "op4" : "Chemical Reactions",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 8,
        "question" : "Who is the author of Life 3.0?",
        "answer" : "Max Tegmark",
        "op1" : "Yual Noah Harari",
        "op2" : "Max Tegmark",
        "op3" : "Carl Sagan",
        "op4" : "Richard Feynman",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 9,
        "question" : "Which type of quantity is Moment of Intertia",
        "answer" : "Tensor",
        "op1" : "Scalar",
        "op2" : "Vector",
        "op3" : "Tensor",
        "op4" : "Unknown",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 10,
        "question" : "Which of the following technologies are more used in blockchain development?",
        "answer" : "Hashing and Linked Lists",
        "op1" : "Hashing and Binary Tree",
        "op2" : "Hashing and Linked Lists",
        "op3" : "Stack and Queues",
        "op4" : "Binary Search and Binary Tree",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 11,
        "question" : "Which of the following players belong to PSG (according to the date 21 Aug 2021)?",
        "answer" : "Neymar, Messi and Mbappe",
        "op1" : "Neymar, Mohd. Salah and Luis Suarez",
        "op2" : "Sadio Mane, Paul Pogba and Lewandowski",
        "op3" : "Neymar, Messi and Mbappe",
        "op4" : "Luka Modrich, Zalatan and Sergio Ramos",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    },{
        "id" : 12,
        "question" : "Who won Ballon dor 2020?",
        "answer" : "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "op1" : "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "op2" : "Lionel Messi",
        "op3" : "Neymar Jr.",
        "op4" : "Robert Lewandowski",
        "score" : 0, 
        "selected_option" : ""
    }
]


export default Questions

